Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Power of Everyone
Episode 59
Weslie
Get out of my body
Give Weslie back to us
Let’s opening a portal again
Do you think my world is a place you can just enter whenever you please?
Give Weslie back right now
If you can do it, then give it a try
Weslie, Weslie, wake up, quick.
Who?
He’s waking up.
Who are you?
It’s us.
Oh, it’s you guys.
I…
Where is this?
We finally made it inside.
The core of the device.
So after being absorbed, you have to wait here for the conversion.
We saw a lot of people here who had been completely turned into energy.
Then we need to find a way out.
Look at the state we’re in
What else can we do?
This…
Weslie, there’s nothing you can do either
So, you are just playing around?
I’ve discovered that energies can influence each other
How about we try to disrupt his energy?
So he can’t absorb it
But what good would that do?
I believe my friends are still out there fighting hard
And I, right here,
must also fight alongside them in my own way.
Give Weslie back right now!
It’s useless.
As long as the Absorption Device remains,
it will provide me with a ceaseless supply of energy.
It really is completely useless.
My energy…
I want to see what he can do without any energy.
You guys…
Still couldn’t make it out in time.
We’ve been here for too long.
We’re about to turn into energy ourselves now.
But we’ve decided to channel our remaining energy to you.
Why me?
Last time, you sacrificed yourselves to save me…
The result
Yet I didn’t manage to do anything
No
If it weren’t for you
We never would have made it this far
Because of you, we have a different kind of life
You are the one who can create miracles
Come out
I’m back
How do you have abilities again?
Didn’t your gadget break?
What I’m using now is
everyone’s power
No matter what, it is impossible to defeat me.
Weslie has become so powerful.
We can’t let Weslie fight alone. Let’s go.
My gear
The Wolffy I know isn’t someone who gets discouraged easily
Wolnie
What?
Wolffy has set off?
Wilie, you stay here
I’m going to help Daddy
Good luck, Mommy
Wolnie, that…
I’m sorry
I’ve been thinking lately
If I hadn’t made you clear out your inventions back then…
If only I understood you a little better…
No, it was thanks to you confiscating my gadgets
that I was able to use the boomerang bomb to stop Blue’s scheme.
And now,
I’m going to use the gadgets you brought to save the world.
Wolnie, thank you.
Wolffy,
hurry and come help!
Go ahead, Wolffy.
Wait for my triumphant return, Wolnie.
Make sure you come back safe.
Finish him off in one go.
My turn.
Bear.
Ridiculous. These attacks are nothing more than a tickle.
Size Candy.
Then let me, King Wolffy, give you a good
scratch.
Super Magnet.
Time for you to taste what it’s like to be pulled in.
Give us back our worlds.
It’s finally over.
Wait, no.
There is no way you can defeat me.
Because I…
am this very world.
It feels like he has an endless supply of energy.
How on earth can we stop him?
His energy comes from the Absorption Device in the core layer.
If we can just open the passage to the core layer,
we can destroy the Absorption Device.
You?
Weslie.
Goodbye, Weslie.
Welcome the arrival of my world with your destruction.
Made it just in time.
To be continued